[ti:May You Always Have Positive Thoughts]
[ar:Regina Hill]
[by:湖心小筑]
[00:21.71]May every day of your life bring you fresh hopes for tomorrow---because hopes give us all our reason for trying.
[00:36.87]May each new day bring a feeling of excitement, joy, and a wonderful sense of expectation.Expect the best, and you'll get it.
[00:55.56]May you find peace in simple things, because those are the ones that will always be there.
[01:17.28]May you remember the good times and forget the sorrow and pain, for the good times will remind you of how special your life has been.
[01:36.34]May you always feel secure and loved, and know you are the best.
[02:13.96]May you experience all the good things in life---the happiness of realizing your dreams, the joy of feeling worthwhile, and the satisfaction of knowing you've succeeded.
[02:31.38]May you find warmth in others, expressions of love and kindness, smiles that encourage you, and friends who are loyal and honest.
[02:49.08]May you realize the importance of patience and accept others for what they are. With understanding and love, you'll find the good in every heart.
[03:05.34]May you have faith in others and the ablity to be vulnerable. Open your heart and really share the miracle of love and intimacy.
[03:41.50]Above all, may you always have positive thoughts.
[04:37.66]
